Hey everyone and welcome to my channel! Today's video is about...
AHHHHH! It's alive!
For today's video I need two things. More space and an assistant!
Hello Puxy!
Candy Coated US sent us an inflatable balloon dog.
We're going to try that today and show it to you.
And I will match your outfit I guess.
Shiny black as a dog.
Is this the dog now? It's just the ball. I'm going to unfold it.
Oh wow, it's huge! I think I got the top. I got the tail!
It's over two meters tall so we needed another space, not the usual setup.
And it kind of feels like an inflatable boat.
We have to pump it up with an air pump.
I think it has several inflatable spaces, like the ears, the head, the arms.
The special thing about it is that you can put a person in there.
A person?
A person!
Thank you for being my guinea pig today and trying this.
and thanks to Candy Co. US so they not only do dogs but a lot of creatures and
we sat together last night and watched the safety and instruction video so we
now know what to do I think we know everything about it and yeah let's get
started here we go there's a zipper in the back and Foxy is wearing spandex for
a reason it's slippery there are no sharp edges and you won't touch the
aside with your skin all the way of course I think it's more comfortable this way
so they said to get in with the feet first
all the way down to the
yeah when you're there yeah because there are these
bubble shaped foot so structures yeah nope nope we're getting there
So this is a tube where I'm gonna breathe through.
It's like a snorkel basically.
Yeah, and there are some holes for some visibility.
It's better to do this with two persons
because it's easier and there's someone who can help
if something goes wrong.
There are several safety measures in place.
There's an emergency valve on the inside.
And I think it's easier to close the zipper in the bag
with the second person, not by yourself.
Sure.
There are great instruction videos and safety videos
from Candy Coaters.
You should definitely watch them before you wear one.
You can also take a ceramic cutter in your hand
on the inside to cut yourself free
if there's really an emergency.
Yeah, now we're going to try this, I guess.
We're going.
Tail.
Careful with the hair!
Alright, you can
knot your head
also when it's pumped up and you can move your arms.
got my electric pump here let's start
Tada! I did it! I blew her up! And you can move around, yes. I didn't want to over blow
it or blow it up too much because the more you blow it up the more restricting it is
of course on the inside. Although I didn't want to overdo it for the first try. Can you
say something? Not really. But can you see something? You can nod or shake your head. No,
close your eyes. Okay. Can you turn around like one full turn? So you can move, that's fine.
Oh it's so great!
Oh the tail! So lovely!
I also did not push in all the valves because as I said we're trying this for the first time so I didn't want to risk anything yet so we familiarize ourselves now.
It's so cute!
With a little nose.
Nice! Cute!
Hey, she hit me!
Nice! So shiny!
And black!
My hair is now static.
Okay, so this is by the way the hole where she breathes through.
And I'm going to release all the walls now and get her out of it.
Head first.
And ears.
And the neck.
Bottom.
Other arm.
Leg.
Tail.
Other leg.
And now I'm going to open this.
Oh she's completely sweaty.
It's not sweat.
This looks like a costume now, you know the dinosaur costume.
The inflatable ones.
Well, getting in there took much more time than getting out there.
Definitely with all the blowing up everything, even though we had the electric air pump.
How are you feeling?
Are you okay?
I couldn't see a thing.
Did you close your eyes?
I had to.
There was a lot of pressure in my face.
I felt the cold air that you blow in.
Oh, so it got colder?
A little bit, not that much.
But could you breathe okay?
Breathing was totally fine.
I think I left my whole makeup face in there.
That's fine, it looks fine.
We can clean that out.
Was it warm on the inside after a while?
No, like the temperature in the room, not that warm.
So it's not like latex. The air between the...
Mounds? The air in the dock?
The air in the dock.
Yeah, kept the temperature of the room so not that sweaty or cold or stuff like that.
It was okay-ish.
Okay-ish? Okay-ish. Yeah, I haven't thought that I can move that much.
Yeah, it was good.
So the arms couldn't go closer than this, but the rest was totally fine.
Nice, okay.
Would you do it again?
For a photoshoot, sure.
I think I really like the look and how it could look on photos.
Yeah, when he takes together or something.
For my private pleasure, I wouldn't, I guess.
I think it's a very special kink.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, it's fun to try it out.
Thank you again for doing this.
Thank you for having me for such an interesting thing.
Well, you thought it was cute.
Let's get you out.
Super fast.
Even in case of emergency I would have gotten you out in seconds.
I felt safe in every second.
Thank you for keeping an eye on me.
Yeah, sure.
Alright.
we're done here. I hope you could enrich your day with this and beauty. I hope you will get some more of these in different shapes and colors.
You want to try it again? I want the squeaky nose. The squeaky nose? Sorry about the squeaky nose and I really want to do that.
Okay, yeah. So there's the squeaky nose available for these balloon animal dogs. And again, please watch the safety videos if you get one.
one and please take care of yourself don't put yourself in unnecessary danger
you got a second person all that and have fun while trying this out yeah see you in the next video
okay see you in the next video follow her on instagram
bye